How much sleep do you need?
你需要多少睡眠呢？
Do you find that if you don‘t get enough shut-eye and wake up feeling dopey, you spend the rest of the day in a bad mood?
你有没有发现，如果你没有足够的睡眠，醒来后感觉昏昏沉沉的，那么你接下来一整天的心情都会不好呢？
I certainly need my eight hours a night and that’s important according to research, because bad sleep isn‘t good for our health.
我当然需要每晚八小时的睡眠，而且根据研究，这是很重要的，因为睡眠不好对我们的健康没有好处。
We all need a good night’s rest to recharge our batteries, but according to the Sleep Council in the UK, the average Briton gets six-and-a-half hour‘s sleep a night, which for most people is not enough.
我们都需要好好睡一晚来恢复体力，但是根据英国睡眠委员会的说法，英国人平均每晚睡六个半小时，这对大多数人来说是不够的。
It’s tempting to cut back on the sleep we get, after all there are plenty of other more fun or useful things to be doing.
我们很容易减少睡眠时间，毕竟还有很多其他更有趣或更有用的事情要做。
Sometimes the pressure of work or a long commute means that our head hits the pillow much later than it should.
有时候，工作压力或长时间的通勤意味着我们上床睡觉的时间比应该的时间晚得多。
But lots of studies have shown that cutting back on sleep, deliberately or otherwise, can have a serious impact on our bodies.
但是很多研究表明，不管是有意还是无意地减少睡眠时间，都会对我们的身体产生严重的影响。
Studies have proved that sleep deprivation has a negative effect on our bodies but it can also have an effect on our mental health.
研究已经证明，睡眠不足对我们的身体有负面影响，但它也会对我们的心理健康产生影响。
A BBC programme called Trust Me, I‘m a Doctor ran an experiment with the University of Oxford and was surprised to discover how quickly the mood of the people they were testing changed when their sleep was restricted to four hours a night for just three nights.
英国广播公司一档名为《相信我，我是医生》的节目与牛津大学进行了一项实验，他们惊讶地发现，当被测试者连续三个晚上每晚只睡四个小时时，他们的情绪变化得有多快。
Doctoral student, Sarah Reeve, who ran the experiment, said: “There were increases in anxiety, depression and stress, also increases in paranoia and feelings of mistrust about other people”.
进行这项实验的博士生莎拉·里夫说：“焦虑、抑郁和压力增加了，偏执以及对他人的不信任感也增加了。”
This and other research into the mental health of students, has found that the lack of sleep increases our negative emotions.
这项研究以及其他针对学生心理健康的研究发现，睡眠不足会增加我们的负面情绪。
I know that when I’m sleep deprived, it is harder to feel positive about things or even think straight!
我知道，当我睡眠不足时，很难对事情感到乐观，甚至很难清晰地思考！
Daniel Freeman, professor of clinical psychology at Oxford University, agrees that insomnia is bad for our brain.
牛津大学临床心理学教授丹尼尔·弗里曼也认为，失眠对我们的大脑有害。
He says: “We have more negative thoughts when we‘re sleep-deprived and we get stuck in them”.
他说：“当我们睡眠不足时，我们会有更多的负面想法，而且我们会陷入这些想法中。”
Bad sleep doesn’t automatically mean you‘ll get mental health issues but other studies have shown that depriving people of enough sleep for only a few nights in a row can be enough to put healthy adults into a pre-diabetic state.
睡眠不好并不一定会意味着你会有心理健康问题，但是其他研究表明，连续几个晚上剥夺人们足够的睡眠就足以让健康的成年人进入糖尿病前期状态。
So with all this evidence maybe we should concentrate on sleeping well.
所以，有了这些证据，也许我们应该专注于好好睡觉。
This means going to bed at a sensible time and creating the right environment in the bedroom to relax and sleep in.
这意味着要在合理的时间上床睡觉，并在卧室里营造一个合适的环境来放松和入睡。
There’s also the modern distraction of using smartphones and tablets at bedtime, tempting us to stay awake.
还有现代的干扰因素，比如在睡觉前使用智能手机和平板电脑，这会诱使我们保持清醒。
The blue light emitted by electronic devices makes us feel less sleepy.
电子设备发出的蓝光会让我们感觉不那么困。
And using them stimulates our brain when it should be winding down.
而且在我们的大脑应该放松的时候使用这些设备会刺激我们的大脑。
What helps you get a good night‘s sleep?
什么能帮助你睡个好觉呢？